Guide to the Frank Lovell Papers TAM.204
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Political Activities and Writings
  - Rivera, Diego; CLA Panels & Reports and Trotsky, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Lovell: Articles, Reviews, Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - FIT Educational Series: WWII & the Division of Europe, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - American Communism - Early Days, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - FIT Caucus in Solidarity, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Series III: FOIA Files
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Files: Frank and Sarah Lovell, undated (Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Files: Sarah Lovell, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)